<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>List of all info pages on SEMDIAL</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/</link><description>Recent content in List of all info pages on SEMDIAL</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://semdial.org/anthology/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Information for Submitters</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/contrib/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/contrib/</guid><description>This page contains general information about how to submit proceedings to the ACL Anthology. If you are a chair whose job it is to submit your conference proceedings, this page should be helpful to you.
Overview of the Submission Process Please contact the Anthology Director as soon as possible to register your intention to submit your proceedings. We will work with you to
assign workshop or conference IDs, determine a publication date, come up with a timeline for draft and final ingestion, and help you to understand the ingestion process.</description></item><item><title>Twenty More Years of Computational Linguistics</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/reflections-aj/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/reflections-aj/</guid><description>The title can be read in two ways. Either I should comment on the past twenty years of ACL (which coincide with the period between ACL 1982 held at Penn and ACL 2002 also held at Penn) or twenty more years from ACL 2002. As you will see many of my comments will be relevant to both these interpretations.
How did I get into computational linguistics (CL)? I did not really get into it.</description></item><item><title>ACL 1993—1994</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/reflections-ksj/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2002 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/reflections-ksj/</guid><description>As an organisation, the ACL has clearly evolved over the forty years since its foundation. (Whether, or how, it has evolved in its area of intellectual interest over the same period is a tricky and interesting question.) The ACL&amp;rsquo;s organisational development in the period up to Don Walker&amp;rsquo;s death in 1993 was, however, rather different from its evolution since. This was partly because the ACL&amp;rsquo;s community was not very large in its first two decades, partly because there were only three Secretary-Treasurers in the whole period from 1963 to 1993.</description></item><item><title>Requesting Corrections</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/corrections/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/corrections/</guid><description>The staff of the ACL Anthology can process requests for both errata and revisions for scholarly works that are already published. These are processed at a lower priority than normal ingestion, maintenance, and development work for the Anthology, but will be processed in due course. While this service can help correct post-publication problems, due to certain difficulties and liabilities, the corrections have certain limitations, which we describe here. It is strongly recommended to ensure your work is correct when published.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/credits/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is run entirely by contributions from volunteers. We are grateful to all our contributors whose work makes this collection of scholarly papers freely available to all.
Active Volunteers Arya McCarthy (Johns Hopkins University) &amp;mdash; MIT Press Ingestion Lead Arne Köhn (Universität des Saarlandes) Chenliang Li (Wuhan University) &amp;mdash; Journal Indexing Lead Daniel Gildea (University of Rochester) David Chiang (University of Notre Dame) &amp;mdash; Data Lead Kilian Gebhardt (TU Dresden) Marcel Bollmann (University of Copenhagen) &amp;mdash; Site Development Lead Martín Villalba (Saarland University) &amp;mdash; System Administrator Past Volunteers Animesh Prasad (National University of Singapore) Anoop Sarkar (Simon Fraser University) Christian Federmann (Microsoft Research) Christoph Teichmann (Bloomberg LLC) Hien Linh Nguyen (Facebook Singapore) Nitin Madnani (Educational Testing Services) Simone Teufel (Cambridge) Tao Chen (Google) Authors of anthology introductions: John Nerbonne, Julia Hirschberg, Donia Scott, Diane Litman, Sergei Nirenburg, Karen Spärck Jones, and Aravind Joshi.</description></item><item><title>Help Shape the ACL Anthology!</title><link>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/volunteer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://semdial.org/anthology/info/volunteer/</guid><description>The ACL Anthology is a treasure. It is the repository of our community&amp;rsquo;s scientific contributions extending back over fifty years; its engine is nicely designed custom in-house software that still works well after almost two decades; and it has enabled research projects examining topics like author networks and topic shift over time. That all of this labor has been donated by its members further distinguishes the Anthology: it is not a found treasure, but one that has been crafted and shaped over countless hours, as if by a hundred Berninis, holding keyboards instead of chisels.</description></item></channel></rss>